Ahh ahh ooh ah
Play the game
Who's gonna win or lose this time round?
Kings and Queens put on your poker face.
You're bluffin',
Two-faced, I see through your façade,
So go all out
We doin' this my way!
(Uh) Wanted me to hang it up lay off?
(Uh) Why you so afraid I'mma take off?
Restrictions, oh you're no fun!
Play it, fake it, eh
Ah, Ah, You're, trapped
You can't react to this,
You're seein'
what I got, you just don't got.
The tension is high
Your, your life's on the line
This adrenaline high,
I-I LOVE IT, LOVE IT
I-I see you been tryin'
But you're wastin' your time
Wanna play?
I'll show you I'll
give 'em all a show
You can't stop me, take control
Think you get me? No you don't
Wait till I step in I'm cold
I'mma get up and pose
Switch the game up I know
Got you face-up "oh no!"
Huh? You weren't even close
See me,
Know I always got a trick up my sleeve
Hypnotizing game
See the way that I move move move move
So easy!!
Actually ain't what you perceive
I've got the midas touch,  oh yeah
Come try me baby if you dare (oh-oh-oh).
Hold it, give it up. Baby, try your luck
Cause I'm a show show show off
I don't, don't, don't stop
The tension is high
Your, your life's on the line
This adrenaline high,
I-I LOVE IT, LOVE IT
I-I see you been tryin'
But you're wastin' your time
Wanna play?
I'll show you I'll
give 'em all a show
You can't stop me, take control
Think you get me? No you don't
Wait till I step in I'm cold
I'mma get up and pose
Switch the game up I know
Got you face-up "oh no!"
Huh? You weren't even close
"O-Oh no!" Gunnin' for you I'm so cutthroat
"O-Oh no!" Baby ,Wicked I'm a WILDCARD
"O-Oh no!" I know how this is gonna go
"O-Oh no!" Baby, Wicked I'm a WILDCARD
Eh eh eh eh, ah ah ah ah
Ah ah ah ah aah
give 'em all a show
You can't stop me, take control
Think you get me? No you don't
Wait till I step in I'm cold
I'mma get up and pose
Switch the game up I know
Got you face-up "oh no!"
Huh? You weren't even close
"O-Oh no!" Gunnin' for you I'm so cutthroat
"O-Oh no!" Baby ,Wicked I'm a WILDCARD
"O-Oh no!" I know how this is gonna go
"O-Oh no!" Baby, Wicked I'm a WILDCARD