Previously on Hololive Error
y'all doing fine?
Well, I'm not sure about myself though.
Here goes nothing.
Begin.
Uh…
WHA-
YEET!
UWARGH!
What…
really happened?
Wait, I see a leg.
Something's not right.
Wha-
Huh?
Nani [What]?
What's going on?
UWARGH!!!
Who are you?
WHA-
Eh?
Wait, there's multiple endings to this game?
Right.
Let's try to get the second ending.
Morning.
There's a note here.
Okay.
Relax.
Relax, Mel.
You've seen us before.
Hello.
What if we ignore her and we walk forward?
What would she do if we just kept walking forward?
UGH-
She's still there.
Wait.
We can ignore her for now.
See if that changes anything.
B-d-b-d-b-d-b-d-
Shut up.
Alright.
F-
Fuck me, that still gets me.
What the hell.
Oh.
Here we go.
It's about god-fucking-damn time.
Okay.
Fweeeh.
Still gets me.
So, previously,
we went forward and the whole thing went dark.
What if we take a different route?
I- I know I haven't walked here
in the- in the-
in my first run.
So this is my fir- my- my first run here, then.
It's a note.
Note from a certain-
She's here.
"You don't need to suffer like this anymore.
It wasn't your fault.
I'm gonna make sure nothing like that ever happens in this town again.
Which is why..."
Okay, so we got a brand new note.
We got a brand new note.
That- we have not had that note, okay?
We have not had that note.
Wha-
The lights just went on.
Hello?
What happened here?
Oh no, it's that- it's that thing again.
It's the landslide again.
Lights went up, and I heard steps.
Who the fuck are you?!
I see tables.
Art room?
Okay, we have not been here before.
On the first run, we have not been here before.
Nothing in the canvas.
Right.
Wha-
Who's that?
Wait, who-
"My head hurts.
What's happening to me?
I paint, and I paint, but everything comes out looking wrong.
Is this truly the best I can do?"
[To chat] Hello, Xoly.
Oh, it's gone dark.
Here we are, in the shrine.
Nope,
we haven't gotten anything different.
I just went to grab some candy so I can chew on to it.
But hilariously-
Hilariously, there's one candy that just stood out to me,
and I just had to try it, even though it tastes horrible right now.
So this candy that I found is a double corn candy.
You heard me, it's literally corn.
Like, what the heck?
Why do people make candy out of corn?
It tastes so weird.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, who was that?
It's the dude A, right?
Alright, let's keep walking.
Let's keep walking quickly.
Typical Southeast Asian behavior.
Uh, let's- let's- uh, let's-
Why- why did I forget about that part?
I got scared about that on the first run.
That happened to me again.
Alright, let's look around.
Let's check- check if there's anything.
An unopened milk carton.
Hololive chocolate?
Chocolate?
Did you say chocolate?
Chocolate?!
Okay.
And there's a note.
"You can't go that way you can't go that way you can't go that way you can't go that way.
Who's this 'Yuka' person
Who's this 'Yuka' person?"
Oh!
Okay…
Here she is.
There's a note right where she's sitting.
Oh no!
We were supposed to grab it!
Okay, let's try going through it as fast as we can.
So, we have very, very little time window to grab the note.
Two…
Three…
And…
Four.
Walk up.
Oh, there it is!
We got the note, we got the note!
"If you want to change something, you need to take action.
I know that, but I didn't used to think that way."
Okay, we got it, we got it!
Okay, nobody is in the room.
Oh, there's a chair.
There's an extra chair.
Wha-
What is she doing here?
She disappeared.
Why was she here?
Why?
What is she doing here?
There is a door banging.
Wha-
Okay, it's different now.
Our first ending used to have a cutscene.
I think there's more to this now.
Chapter 8.
So, we're on a-
Oh, fuck me, the landslide is happening again.
What is it this time?
Oh, no.
So, this is everything together in one place.
Wait, can we go through when the door-
No, we cannot.
What's going on?
Hey, yo.
Uh…
This is a whole lot different than the first run.
I-
And there's a note here.
WARGH!!!
Jesus Christus.
Okay, so we got a note.
"Record of Grandfather's investigation. "Cause of the Supernatural Phenomena"
I haven't been feeling well since I started investigating the woods.
For days on end, I've been wracked by constant headaches.
I can't think of any other explanation than those woods.
Are the spirits of the people buried there taking vengeance on the living?
Come to think of it, there's an old shrine in Aogami.
Maybe I'll find some clues there.
It's worth looking into."
It's getting more and more chaotic now.
Oh, no.
Huh?
What are you doing here?
Woah.
This is way different than I thought.
This second ending has more stuff going on.
Okay, this is-
I thought I could brave up because I already know what-
how the game is going to go, but-
Turns out there's more stuff packed into it than I thought.
It's that dog girl.
Okay.
And the door is open.
Any notes?
Has she left any notes?
No?
Multiple knockings?
And hands?
Nani (What)?
What?
What's going on?
Yuka.
Okay.
It has been played out to us again.
That piece of history.
Okay, train stops.
Okay.
What are we expecting?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
What's going on?
We're back in school again.
Aogami High in present time.
I shouldn't be in this-
In this time?
In this time frame?
What do you mean?
This is the present time.
Nande [Why]?
Why?
Why are you here for?
Why are you after me for?
What is going on?
A note.
Rubbled school.
"I feel like my head's going to burst.
Is that the shrine?
Is that over the-
must be.
I see.
It all makes sense now.
It's the
Aono...mi...
So this is...
fate that...
who arrive...
the truth.
I must conti...
Whoa!
Must go through- Oh no.
He went through.
You don't say.
I- I think I know what's up with this-
With that dude now.
Why?
Why are you stopping us?
What is it that you're hiding?
Tell me!
Is this all
just a dream?
Who is it?
She's here!
Okay!
Fuck me that-
Ending 2?
I still don't understand.
Why?
So there's something different going on
in chapter- chapter 5.
That's probably-
That's probably ending number 3.
We're missing a note.
Two notes.
I- I think we might be able to find these
on- on- on- on the third ending.
Oh it is!
Look at that!
Chapter 8 is a- is a longer one.
Like, okay.
I see.
Right.
Interesting.
There's still something that gets me curious.
Like, who- who was the-
who's the one that's cursifying Aogami?
Like, who's the culprit behind it?
Why did they do this?
What is the- what is the grand motive?
This still left me very very curious.
Extremely curious.
I'm gonna relax, clear my head,
and um, thank you guys-
thank you all for watching.
This is the first time I've actually
gone really far with planning out a stream.
The funniest part about planning out a stream though,
is that it took me-
I mean I- I- I only started doing all the planning
literally yesterday.
I've done everything starting yesterday, so this is like- this is like
some sort of like a ch- a self-challenge of how to set up
a fully elaborate stream in all- all in- in a matter of 24 hours.
Isn't it nuts that content creators these days can now set up-
set up crazy elaborate things in a short period of time?
Well I'm- I'm surprised too because of how- how much- how much I'm able to do
even- even with my rusty skills.
So...
But- but yeah.
Man I'm talking too much.
I- I'll talk more about it on- on the next stream.
But yeah.
Thank you all so much for watching.
And as always,
take care.
Have a good night!
This is not the end yet!
VEhJU0lTTk9UVEhFRU5E
Pog su A uskx?
Poil qk gvx flervqz vn lpaf?
Yvz std V yghd, mx'f Vapvg'a xniem!
B rmhb lembgn erq wkfqfo...
Lom bckg rhg'a kig lm hb std!
Xcmjggas maprof val'a bckg hkrprk gr fhsw njvsgwz...
Ubb std fvx ahw hbqx pa
LOM ZIK PIKLLH YF DES!!!
B dwf'b xbfzbci lru...
Lom owf'g thknix gkbz.
B dqdt enyx lbvi fkx ymemeoskl...
XCMJGLUWGZ ZLI UDL KWFM XBF NL!!!
B dwf'b xbfzbci lru...
Lom owf'g thknix gkbz.
B dqdt enyx lbvi fkx ymemeoskl...
XCMJGLUWGZ ZLI UDL KWFM XBF NL!!!
B dwf'b xbfzbci lru...
Lom owf'g thknix gkbz.
B dqdt enyx lbvi fkx ymemeoskl...
XCMJGLUWGZ ZLI UDL KWFM XBF NL!!!
B dwf'b xbfzbci lru...
Lom owf'g thknix gkbz.
B dqdt enyx lbvi fkx ymemeoskl...
XCMJGLUWGZ ZLI UDL KWFM XBF NL!!!