*sigh*
(Glass skirt chase ensues)
(Pushing the ONE bubble off be like...)
*gives up*
Dokibird: Heeeyyy~
(Old man screams)
Doki: Heh hah haha~
*sigh* What a video for a bit.
This is the iPhone 17 Pro Max.
When I was watching the keynote, dreadfully honest,
there were a lot of keynote norms that got me bored as heck.
But when we got to the base iPhone 17, something changed.
*During the WWDC Watchalong stream*
Hey, we're getting to the vanilla.
wasu: "unlike anything" and then it's the same
Yeah, it is the same.
It's nighttime. That's unreal.
That's unreal.
We're showing the 17 at nighttime??
Nat: Yeah
Sorry, the vanilla at nighttime.
Hold on.
Lav-lavender is really nice.
I like that.
Nat: Yeah, I like that too.
Classic ProMotion.
So they did bring ProMotion over.
Classic.
Nat: Yep, that one can be crossed out, hold on.
All right.
*ding*
Adaptive refresh rate, huh?
And of course, they're going to do that same animation,
but just on the 17.
wasu: oh nice the goofy graphs are here
"The goofy graphs are here."
Real, goofy graph.
(Nat chuckles)
Correction: Fourty-EIGHT MP
46 megapixels, okay.
Really? The telephoto is still 12
na-
megapixels?
God damn it.
You know what I just realized?
Girl, you ain't using the camera button.
(Mel laughing)
The displays are now 120 hertz, Super Retina XDR,
Ceramic Shield 2 glass, square front camera sensors.
The fact that these are all on the base iPhones,
kind of reducing reasons to get a Pro for an average person.
Well, I'm no average person.
I only get a new phone whenever a phone gets discontinued
or when I got lucky and that my savings allows.
This is an exception,
especially when all the past iPhone upgrades
are minuscule increments
and that you have vapor chamber cooling on the pro phones,
which supposedly spreads the heat more evenly,
allowing for longer sustained loads.
I suppose that's how hot it gets.
We've reached that point, guys.
Aside from the vapor chamber,
there's 12 gigs of RAM instead of eight.
There's ProRes RAW, meaning I can adjust the exposure in post
whenever I screw up something.
And...
we don't talk about the camera button.
Three cameras, so there's dedicated lens for each,
but allegedly it doesn't improve from the last generation.
But for someone like me who came from the 12 Pro Max,
there should be a jump of quality
from 12 megapixel across the board
to 48, also across the board.
Obvious things out of the way, let's get hands on with the phone.
One thing I did want to find out is the charging part of the phone.
In the keynote, they said it can charge to 50%
in 20 minutes with a 40 watt charger.
(slams desk)
Let's find that out.
Right, so the reason why I'm bringing in this Baseus power bank
is because it has a wattage indicator.
While it is not exactly professional,
however, it is quite enough to show me basic information
to see how much it charges, I guess.
So let's have a look how much it charges.
Well, unfortunately, I can't find out how much it charges,
unfortunately, primarily because I got 74% battery,
so it's currently trickle charging,
but at least we can see that it trickles at 17 watts, probably
16, 15, it's going back and forth, I suppose.
However, to charge this phone at its optimal speed of 40 watts,
Parrotting a Chinese equivalent of LTT
but filmography focused tech tuber, Mediastorm,
check their coverage out too,
you need specifically a USB PD 3.2 charger
(USB PD 3.2 Charger)
which has two key features,
which are SPR, standard power range,
SPR = Standard Power Range
(Allows power up to 100w, but this iPhone can only do 40w)
and AVS, adjustable voltage source.
AVS = Adjustable Voltage Supply*
(Allows scaling voltages per small steps)
*For some reason, it's either "Supply" or "Source"
This is a hyper new standard and it's way ahead of its time,
so it'll be some long periods of time before it becomes a norm,
unless you're willing to shell out $39 for Apple's own charger.
Erhhh...Which... personal opinion, I would not,
because in Mediastorm's own test, even without AVS,
(Seriously, check them out! English subtitles available)
you'd still be able to reach almost similar charging speeds,
within the 20 minutes of charging that they have done.
Now let's get the power bank out of the way.
I'm going to take a second to address people's complaints
as they watched the intro.
Why is there a hole in the screen protector?
There's possibly only one reason why that might be the case.
That's because I have not actually applied
the screen protector prior to this,
and I've already begun using the phone.
So, there's a high chance that
I might have not cleaned the screen properly.
So, I'm going to try to clean the screen again
and reinstall the screen protector properly.
Hopefully there's an update video.
Update Mel?
Heya, Update Mel here.
I've come bearing great news.
Safe to say, I've removed the bubbles from the screen protector.
Now back to you, main video Mel.
Thanks, Update Mel.
And secondly, why a silicone case and a screen protector?
Well, as a full-blown Asian,
I have the mindset to ensure the phone's resale value
is as high as possible,
even when I have zero intentions of selling the phone.
I don't think that's the right way to put it.
I guess you could say...
I handle it like an overprotective person
and prefer the phone to be as mint as possible,
while letting the accessories take the hit
for whatever mishaps that might happen.
Let's address the second elephant in the room.
The A19 Pro SoC.
Let's get the boring parts out of the way.
Apple Intelligence?
Yeah, that's it.
If you want to know more about it,
there's other creators that explain it better.
I, unfortunately, am only interested in
making automation convenient, not generating slop.
Networking chip.
There are two ways I connect my phone:
WiFi and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Let's just say that financial decisions
did not allow me to have a router in my studio.
And the reception (coming) from outside the studio is abysmal.
Yeah.
This is actually the closest server that I could find.
On a serious note, let's test the Ethernet speed.
Oh yeah, this is pretty decent in my opinion.
Let's do a side-by-side speed test
with my old iPhone and my new iPhone,
somewhere near the router.
Take it away, FutureMel.
Hey yeah, FutureMel here.
So I've done my testings near the router, as I mentioned previously,
and I find the results kind of confusing to me.
It's probably because the brand new Apple N1 chip
that was supposed to be replacing Qualcomm's in-house chips.
(not "in-house", wth am I saying?)
My best assumption is that the N1 chip is not quite mature just yet.
Because, based on the results that I've gotten,
I've got a pretty consistent speed of 500Mbps, give or take a little bit.
However, it's a little bit slower on the 17 Pro Max.
There may be some other factor at play,
probably because of my router's weird beamforming,
or something else.
But across the span of 5 different testings,
I've gotten consistently the same results.
So, your mileage may vary.
However, I did feel, probably it's a placebo effect,
that I got better WiFi reception signal
from the 17 Pro Max over the 12.
But, I did not really do a synthetic test,
so I'm not sure if what I'm feeling is true.
So, again, your mileage may vary once again.
So back to you, main video Mel.
Thanks, PastMel.
Now on to gaming.
I'm a filthy gacha gamer.
However, I do play games that flames mobile GPU.
So this is perfect.
I'm gonna be testing Genshin and Zenless Zone Zero for that.
I gotta make it clear that testing Genshin is insanely subjective.
Many of the benchmarks like Denki, Linus Tech Tips, and a few others,
fail to mention the locations they're walking in when doing the test,
making the test results inconsistent.
Another factor making it inconsistent
is that miHoYo devs can continue to optimize
the very location you're walking in as versions pass.
So let's do it in three locations.
Mondstadt Plains, Dragonspine, and Fontaine.
On these specific versions on screen.
Genshin ver: 6.0.0
ZZZ ver: 2.2.0
iOS ver: 26.0.1
I'll go through why for each locations as I show the test footage,
which are all captured from the capture card.
Heya, this is the other Mel with testing footages.
Let's go through how I'm going about with this setup.
The graphics settings should be pretty much maxed out
with no motion blur, but frame rate capped specifically to 60 frames,
to make this test consistent
between the iPhone 12 Pro Max and the 17 Pro Max.
I feel like virtually every tests I've observed
has been done with a freshly created account
with no preparation form the reviewer's end.
So, I'm gonna do it a little differently.
I'm doing it with my personal account,
but with a little more constant variables than the reviewers.
You see, most reviewers have either Traveler Lumine or Aether
or Amber as their active character.
I'm going to fixate that variable
by just having Anemo Lumine in the team.
Why would this be important?
That's because there are 5-star characters like Raiden Shogun
and Mavuika with explosive particles
that will change the factor for this specific test.
However, we're not leaving them out.
Although I don't have them.
As we're going through the test of frame rates with my usual lineup
to compare as well, which are Beidou, Barbara, Ganyu, and Klee.
Now for all of you Genshin spreadsheet gamers out there,
just let me be, okay?
This is my daily driver.
And lastly, we're also going on the fixed route,
Don't worry, we will get to it eventually on each location.
all while starting the march from specifically
12pm game world time.
Unfortunately on iOS,
while there was a way to get the statistic HUD out,
shoutout to MrMacRight for the tool,
this tool only enables the HUD set up by Apple.
And one sanctioned information that we don't get precise info of
would be the core temperatures.
So throughout the test, we'll be referring
to the thermal strategy the SoC will be on,
which is Apple's way to vaguely explain
how much they're thermally throttling the chip.
Here's the following explanation in the way I paraphrase them.
Nominal, ideal conditions where the SoC can run at full speed.
Never happens throughout the test.
Fair, the SoC is aware that it's heating up
and it's up to the app to self-throttle.
Serious, the app should begin throttling, if it can,
to bring the thermals down,
which never happens with games like this.
And lastly, critical, the app needs to do whatever it takes
to bring it down for reals,
including disabling the camera if it needs to.
Thankfully, never happened during the test.
You might also notice next to the resolution
that the display mode on the iPhone 12 Pro Max says "Direct",
while the 17 says "Composited".
These don't really make any performance difference during my test,
but they're different because
the iPhone 12 Pro Max was connected
to the Apple official HDMI adapter,
while the 17's got my TP-Link Type-C hub.
One's sending the display feed directly
to the adapter and capture card,
and another's composited before outputting to the USB hub.
With that out of the way, let's get right to the test.
Test #1 & #2: Mondstadt Plains (Genshin)
Mondstadt Plains.
The Plains is the single most prominent testing location,
most notably, the pathway just outside the domain
outside the gate of Mondstadt,
*correct me if I'm wrong*
as well as the beach
where Traveller fished Paimon out on the first day.
Now you see, this area is mostly tested by most tech-tubers,
so I figured I'd at least set a constant
that I can always refer to should I make another benchmark
with another device or computer.
So on the iPhone 12 Pro Max, as I booted up the game
and prepared the testing spot,
the thermals quickly shot up to serious just before testing.
After attempting to blow the device
with an intense amount of room temperature air with a blower,
it didn't bring the temperatures down.
I tried again with ice pack.
That didn't help either.
So I decided to just keep going with the test,
after putting adequate amount of chill
into the body of the phone, predominantly where the SoC was at.
As we keep going down this path,
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
the frame rate drops and hovers around 47 frames,
And kept there, but the stutter is well evened out
and feels consistent,
which could also mean there's no major lag spikes just yet.
Security Officer Peña: Bye, have a great time!
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
But sit tight, this is just the Mondstadt plains,
Security Officer Peña: !emit taerg a evah ,eyB
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
where it's the most optimized.
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
On the iPhone 17 Pro Max, as expected of the major jump of SoCs,
we're seeing only fair thermals,
and the frame rate is consistently 60 frames.
There's not much to write home about, but yeah, very nice.
From the beach, after putting an Ice Pack on the iPhone 12 Pro Max,
I got going right away,
and just after a while, the thermals caught up to the SoC
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
and began throttling once again.
So if you're playing this under a sunny weather,
you might want to consider holding it off
till you go back inside.
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
Whereas the new iPhone 17 Pro Max,
because of the vapor chamber cooling,
the heat was evenly spread across the unibody chassis,
and while it's kind of warm to the touch at the plateau,
it's not steaming hot like the 12 Pro Max
where the SoC is without a heat spreader,
like a heat pipe or a vapor chamber.
Test #3: Mondstadt Dragonspine (Genshin)
Now onto Dragonspine,
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
I'm gonna do my test specifically along the path up to the tree,
while getting enemy attention from a nearby camp.
This used to be my old way to test out the mixed environmental snow
and particles from the enemies.
In the past, this place in my personal experience was a GPU flamer,
to the point where the GPU would artifact
or glitch out for a frame or two
during Beidou's skills or Barbara's ultimate.
But as we can see nowadays, it's pretty optimized for both phones,
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
albeit some hitches from the usual suspect.
Just like the test in Mondstadt Plains,
we're expecting the same behavior though with another factor
having enemy particles and effects playing in.
However, there is that one odd hitch on the 17 Pro Max.
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
It wasn't quite noticeable during testing,
so I think that was just an odd one out.
I did try out the ultimate effects at Dragonspine
to see how much it affects the performance if I were to have a fight there,
and there was only insignificant hitches on the 17 Pro Max,
and it's already a lagfest before I even start on the 12 Pro Max.
Test #4 & 5: Fontaine - Overlook & Underwater (Genshin)
Fontaine.
Two spots:
From Sumeru, looking towards Fontaine,
and underwater near Chemin de l'Espoir.
Google Translate: Chemin de L'Espoir
The overview of Fontaine is a scenario of simulating large open world,
[Green] = Starting point
albeit with low texture from faraway objects,
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
while being underwater should simulate all the particles
and entities around you while you're swimming.
[Green] = Starting point
Right as I started, the iPhone 12 Pro Max began hitching,
looking at the behavior of the frames from the way I moved the camera at a time,
it looks as if something's in the water below
that's stressing the SoC.
Meanwhile on the 17 Pro Max, it is as what you'd expect,
but there's still something in the water
that's getting to the miniscule number of frames.
I'll disregard that too, as an average person
probably would not be too bothered by that.
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
Underwater is the same as most locations,
nothing to write home about, just something to keep in mind
if you were to buy a second-hand iPhone 12 Pro Max.
I've also tried out Nod Krai for specifically the iPhone 17 Pro Max,
[Green] = Starting point
[Orange] = Route
[Red] = End point
because I got curious and decided to try out Nod Krai
following this specific path.
Since this was a very new location,
I doubt the 12 Pro Max can handle it,
so I've only tested this place with the 17 Pro Max.
As you can see, at the time of filming,
when the map was not optimized enough,
perhaps from the odd texture streaming, major hitches can happen
and this is the reason why I've only tested up to Fontaine
for my Genshin benchmarks.
But hey, it's not unplayable, it's just a tad bit hard.
I've also done some battles in Genshin Impact
through a domain in Liyue, and safe to say,
when the thermals are on "Serious",
it's pretty much as what you'd expect from both devices.
However, after a while, on the 17 Pro Max,
(The thermal went down to "Fair" right after battle lol)
after the temperature has reached "Serious",
*fartttt*
I found that the result screen was severely lagging a little bit.
(The thermal went down to "Fair" right after battle lol)
I don't know what happened there, but it's kinda odd.
Maybe Genshin, you should fix that.
With Genshin out of the way, let's get to Zenless Zone Zero.
For ZZZ, I've only tested two scenarios
because I don't think I'm qualified enough
nor knowledgeable enough to know the best spots to test,
so I've decided to do it in two locations:
The Sixth Street and the Combat Simulation.
Starting off with walking around the Sixth Street,
the iPhone 12 Pro Max starts off fine at "Fair" thermals
with some odd visible hitches from time to time.
After a while later, "Serious" thermals caught up
and hitches predominantly happening
when General Chop's Waterfall Soup Ramen shop is in view.
Meanwhile, it's perfectly fine on the 17 Pro Max.
*fart*
*Except for that
Whereas the battle scene in the simulation
is where the chaos happen from this game.
Lineup: Miyabi, Koleda, Nekomata
Here's my setup because that's my daily driver.
Miyabi happened to be the most effects-rich character
whenever I use her skill.
So, enter lagfest.
On the iPhone 12 Pro Max,
it's just shitting itself whenever the slashing effects are present.
Across multiple runs, the thermal state is constantly on "Serious",
it never went down.
Whereas on the 17 Pro Max,
it took a while before Miyabi's effects take a toll on the frame rate.
*bruh*
Keep in mind that I'm still playing on 60fps cap.
So, I'd personally drop all graphics and keep 120 frames,
just to save on energy while enjoying the ProMotion display.
I also did try walking around a portion of Failume Heights
on the iPhone 17 Pro Max,
and yes, it's pretty good, even with "Serious" thermals.
I'd say that the upgrade was worth it, and it's far more playable.
With all the testings out of the way, back to you main video, Mel.
Thanks, Other Mel.
Now let's get right into the overall body feel.
Well, with the case on, admittedly it feels…
Well, the case do be trash, but I did pay cheap for that.
So... yea...
*incoming soft spoken ASMR*
I did, however, take a good feel of the phone prior.
Streamed on the 28th Sept 2025 (H3VR Stream's aftershow)
Ooh, the phone feels really…
Oh my god, the weight.
Wait, let me just compare that against my iPhone.
Significant, what the fuck.
Hehe...
When people say 20 grams of difference,
I didn't think it would be much heavier like this.
So, we got the action button, let me just click onto it.
*click*
And the volume up, the volume down.
The camera control button.
*click*
Oh, it's like an actual button.
Oh, I thought it was like, I thought it was these, what do you call it?
the haptic press thing that...
that the iPhone 6S used to have or something like that.
Maybe you can tap on some parts of the phone
so we can get the feel of things.
So this is how the whole aluminum, plastic feels-like.
So, they say anodized aluminum, that feels nice.
But I'm not gonna use too much of my fingernails on it.
Maybe tapping onto it, that should be fine.
But I'm not gonna scratch on it because of Scratchgate.
Further readup can be found in iFixIt.
(The Science Behind Scratchgate and What It Means for Repairing the iPhone 17 Pro)
So I'm gonna be extra careful with that.
I know keys is what it takes
to scratch the corners of the plateau to create scratch gate, but…
I'd rather not risk it.
And then we have the cameras.
And the LiDAR blasters, the flash, microphone, really nice.
And then we got the ceramic shield on the back.
Oh, that feels nice.
Like, nobody really talked about this for some reason,
but it looks quite clear-ish.
But it's got a matte finish.
Like, if you scratch on it with your fingernails, it sounds quite matt-y, you know?
it sounds quite matte-y, you know?
Like, listen to this.
It feels similar to the sound of
if you were to scratch a cardboard box.
It's got a full matte finish.
It's not with a screen protector or something like that.
It's just raw Ceramic Shield 1 glass on the back.
And then to where the Apple logo is, it's just pure gloss.
Kinda nice, pretty cool, pretty neat Apple.
As for the front, with the paper sticker cover still on,
it just feels matte-y, I guess.
And I'm just tapping away at the screen.
I'm sure it tickles if the phone were alive.
Alright, let's pull out the…
Oh my god, I just lifted the flap
and I saw Type-C and I go, "Oh my god, this is unreal".
I am leaving the Lightning infrastructure.
This is because the iPhone 12 Pro Max is the last device
that uses Lightning in this household.
I don't think there's any other devices
that is using Lightning in this household,
provided that I have yet to repair my AirPods Gen 3.
I'm hoping to self-repair that one day off-stream
because I don't plan on doing it on-stream.
Because I don't have the expertise to
have the confidence that I'll be able to finish it
by the end of the stream.
So...
yea...
But I'm still hoping to self-repair it one day.
Or at least learn to self-repair it.
But anyways, here goes.
I'm gonna remove the front plastic.
It doesn't make much sound.
Oh my god, that felt unreal.
The island is a lot smaller now.
So it's got a dedicated island spot.
In the one "island", there's a hole-punch camera
and a smaller island containing the array of proximity sensors
and IR dot blaster for TrueDepth (FaceID)
And then the camera hole-punch hole,
so there's two holes in the top now.
Probably gonna annoy me a little bit
for someone who's only used to a single hole punch.
But the finish in the back looks really, really beautiful.
And I'm going to leave my first fingerprint on it.
Hm, unreal.
Is my hand really not that oily?
It doesn't leave much fingerprints on it.
That's interesting.
I'm gonna put my other hand on it.
Maybe that's not…
Hm, (it) doesn't leave much smudges.
That's so interesting.
Whatever they've put on the Ceramic Shield 2,
that's impressive, I guess.
Either that or my hands are just not that oily.
I'm not gonna plan to turn on the phone just yet,
primarily because I'm thinking of
doing all the transfer thing off-stream.
Oh, that's interesting.
I can actually see the reflections of the telephoto lens.
Like, I can actually weirdly see something
at the reflections of the telephoto lens.
*Returning to normal video*
That's kind of fun to see.
Which is why you see this phone
has been already set up beforehand.
Did I trick you guys?
Ehehehe~
I gotta be honest, if you have seen the live stream,
you would understand how I initially felt when I first unboxed the phone.
But after some time, after some time of chilling,
I did feel...
well, this is a really nicely smooth feeling and nicely matte.
I initially thought the Ceramic Shield 1 in the back
feels like just glossy glass,
but it feels matte-y overall
and it feels really, really nice, I gotta be honest.
However, I am in no position to commentate about the cameras.
Do check out MediaStorm's coverage for that.
It's seriously really, really cool.
But it would be nice to have a shot of this set
using the iPhone for a few minutes.
So let's give it a try.
This is how my set looks like on an iPhone 17 Pro Max
filmed using Apple ProRes Log 2.
Unfortunately, because I didn't know you'd need
storage to film in ProRAW, this was filmed in just Dolby Vision.
(But still with Log 2)
The latest format that allows more flexibility, apparently,
though I have not much experience with log editing,
but you might see the transition from
Because it's not filmed in RAW format, I was confined
with certain things being not exposure accurate.
I tried my best to adjust the curves anyway. >.<
before applying the LUT and after applying the LUT.
So let me know what you guys think.
Do you think this looks good?
Editor Mel: ogod kill me, I wished I had filmed this scene
in RAW now...
Now, while we're filming using the iPhone 17 Pro Max,
let's talk about how I felt about using the iPhone 12 Pro Max.
*Himemori Luna
Hey Luna.
And why I've decided to pick up the iPhone 17 Pro Max
instead of any option in the Android market.
Personally, I feel like there's a lot of factors to consider.
Ecosystem being not the factor.
As you may know,
I don't get locked into ecosystems that easily in my past videos.
One of the major factors is whether the software
takes full advantage of the hardware.
I hate the idea of paying for gimmicks that are either
fully powered by computational processing or neural processing.
While there are choices like OxygenOS from OnePlus,
the next few factors is going to be a turning factor for me.
Another factor is consistent update rollouts.
Google has recently been struggling with
third-party manufacturers taking forever
or being too slow at releasing security updates.
So Google decided to just
(Exclusive: Google wants to make Android safer by switching to 'risk-based- security updates)
only ship the highest severity security updates
while the lower ones can wait to cut the amount of work
third-party manufacturers have to do to release updates.
Whereas Apple, they can ship hotfixes to zero-day exploits
in a rapid security response patch pretty quickly.
(Rapid Security Responses in Apple operating systems)
As for privacy, no company is perfect in that department,
but Google is atrocious in this department.
Another factor is the long update upkeep.
It took EU and Google a while to get long feature updates,
and even so, only flagships get them.
With it's last iOS (15) ended on 31st March 2025.
The iPhone 6S holds the record for almost 10 years of official support,
counting both feature and security updates.
And an average iPhone has been maintained for a good 5-7 years,
Final version: iOS 18
with the iPhone XS and XR
being the latest on the chopping block of getting discontinued,
with it being on iOS 18 instead of iOS 26.
Aside from the factors I mentioned earlier, my choice to upgrade now
is heavily driven by the age of iPhone 12 Pro Max
and my private financial situation, which I'll remain private about it.
With the reasoning out of the way,
let's switch the camera back to my usual Fujifilm X-T100.
So, should you buy the iPhone 17 Pro Max?
It's a mixed bag,
and it heavily depended on what phone you're currently using
and what you're going to use it for.
If you're looking for a phone that does a lot,
even if it's hecking niche, then this is for you.
If you're also maximalist in feature but minimalist in device count,
why the fuck not?
If the walled garden ecosystem doesn't bother you one bit,
and you're all of the above I just mentioned, I'd say it's a big buy.
Otherwise, if you're looking for a phone that just works,
unfortunately I'll say get another phone.
Either get the base iPhone 17,
or the OnePlus 13 if you prefer the Android side.
Because in my opinion, there isn't much to look forward to
in the Pro's this time around for an average person,
unless you're looking for the third camera lens
and the vapor chamber cooling for sustained loads.
I'm going to use this as my new daily driver.
And unfortunately, I have to send this 12 Pro Max for battery service
and hand it over to my mom as her new daily driver.
As for you guys who have seen my adventures with the Note 10+,
that's not going anywhere.
I just think that I've milked the phone for content for too much.
And there isn't anything interesting for me to cover at this point.
The battery has aged far,
(Google will let Android power users bypass
upcoming sideloading restrictions)
and Google has been treating the AOSP community
extremely terribly.
There's just little and little that I can do
to actually improve my experience in Android
by rooting and flashing custom ROMs.
All I'm seeing is just roadblocks after roadblocks without a resolution.
So until Google gets a slap in its face and turn around,
I have nothing to cover with this Note 10+,
that doesn't involve me doing yet another factory reset.
However, I'm not leaving Android.
I still remain daily driving both Android and iOS.
It's just that the Android side for me is rough.
I'm currently eyeing on the OnePlus 13 I just mentioned,
should I be lucky again.
Anyways, what do you think
of this coverage of the iPhone 17 Pro Max?
Should I do a long-term usage review?
Let me know in the comments below.
And that's all for this video.
Be sure to subscribe,
be sure to financially support me through Ko-fi, through Throne,
or you would like to subscribe to Proton and...
protect yourself from big tech
by moving some of your daily infrastructures over,
like say VPNs, or your emails,
and all the yada yada yadas.
Proton might be a good place to start.
And if you click the affiliate link down in the description below,
you would not only be supporting Proton,
but you'll also be supporting yours truly, myself.
However, if you don't mind Proton,
you just want to support me, check out Ko-fi.
Or subscribe to YouTube membership if you feel like it.
All Ko-fi, Throne, Proton, and YouTube
all get the same amount of rights to my exclusive content,
which is mostly just early access content
and a few small, tiny gated videos
that don't really affect the general watchability of the channel.
And expect a long delay from now,
because there's a very very long scripted video
that I'm currently working on, so this might take quite long.
I remember mentioning it in the Proton announcement video,
(I am an affiliate of Proton!)
so check out that video if you're curious about it.
I didn't really dive in too much, but all I said is
it was pretty long and expect really really long I guess.
However, I hope you enjoyed this video.
I actually did this video out of whim,
I was initially working on that said long scripted video,
and then people asked for iPhone coverage so I kinda went,
welp, fuck it, this gets the cut in queue.
So, yep, with that said, that should be it, see you guys next time.
I know this bubble is still bothering you guys,
but please, trust me, I'm gonna take care of it.
Yoo~!
[Ko-fi]
StickTV
Xandra~
Robi
Natalie
StickTV
Xandra~
Robi
Natalie
StickTV
Xandra~
Robi
Natalie
Thank you so much for watching!
Want to translate for Mel?
Check out the description for GitHub link!
Thanks for supporting me financially!
[YouTube]
Robi Kivi
[ProtonVPN]
Anonymous
To those who've watched me to the end, what do you think?
This is my SlimeVR VTuber setup.
It's a little jank, I'm a little bit like, sideways
Because I don't know how to center myself properly
without, I don't know, something breaking?
Like I'm looking off angle right now.
You know what? Absolute cinema.
Ehehehe...
There's no finger tracking yet.
Hopefully one day we'll figure something out.
See you guys.