Streamed on 2025 October 8th
Mel: Oh my god, what a start.
Chicken: Right in the back of the head.
(bonk)
STAAAAAAA-
🎵Eric Andre Show - We'll be Right Back🎵
the
gang
plays
peak
Anyways, Kon-Melo, Kon-Melo, Kon-Melo,
Name: Melori Valentine
Sex: Tensei
Pronouns: She/Her
Profile:
> Extremely Bullyable
> Tech Wizardess
> Proton Affiliate
> Do not ask her for free tech support
she will kill you with hammers
> Chair's girlfriend
> Wait is that a grenade
it's ya Tech Wizardess girl, MeloriTensei!
Today's livestream is gonna be a very very odd timing,
primarily because I'm probably the only one with this sleep schedule.
save me
So today, we've got my girlfriend, SqueakyChair.
Name: SqueakyChair
Sex: With your mom
Pronouns: She/Her
Profile:
> Speedrunner (Allegedly)
> Is the only one who has played PEAK before this stream
> Melori's girlfriend
> She keeps asking me for WD40 I don't have any
hello :>
and we got my goofy-ass friend, KZF1
or as simplified known as Chicken.
Nyuuuiiiiinnnnn~
Name: KZ "Chicken" F1
Sex: Always
Pronouns: He/Him
Profile:
> Chronic Funny Mic Syndrome
> Bastard
> Bing Bong enjoyer
> Give me your paypal I will give you headphones
hello
(giggle)
And I would say a good friend and an artist, Dasher.
AAAAAAAAA
Name: Dasher
Sex: Male
Pronouns: He/Him
Profile:
> Artist (Derogatory)
> Always tired
> Good friend
I'm always tired.
Yes, he's always tired.
(giggles)
There you have it, folks.
There we have it.
That's it for the collab.
🎵Da da da da da da~🎵
🎵Thomas the Tank Engine Theme ending🎵
fin
(not really)
Sorry.
(bonk)
Oh my...
OOOOOOOOOOOOOHHH~!
GET REKT
GET SHIT ON
So one thing I did-
(bonk)
ow
One thing I did notice is that umm...
for whatever reason, my mouse moves out of the screen
when I just turn my head way too far,
and I don't think there's a way to fix that.
Yeah, there...
ooh, you touch my tralala....
...except for pressing the escape key twice.
my ding ding dong...
Today, we're gonna be playing PEAK.
I have no idea what to expect because I've seen...
I've seen gameplays, but
it's like everyone's got a different experience.
Where-we're-we're-we're (stuttering)
she's fine
just give her a second
🎵Toby Fox - And Now For Today’s Sponsors…!🎵
We're-we're four idiots.
Woah, did you see that? Did you see that?
Hehe
flight leaves in one second
Holy sh-
Oh?!
So, one of us could just start it right away, huh?
I see.
Oh, where are we?
Ahhh~
Dasher: 'morning people.
Wat da fak?
Good morning, hellscape people.
(bonk)
ow
doooooooooooooooo000
ow my head
dooooooooooooooooooooooo
Scout (da) cannon.
dooooo
Oh look,
I have drugs.
dooooooooooooooooooo
dooooooo
doooooooooooooooooo
What?
Hahahahah
(For) the backpacks, you can only put items in the backpack
when you're not carrying it.
You can't take items in and out of it.
Woah?!
x1
x2
Oh-Okay, what happened?
Stuck the landing
x3
wow! :D
oh
She used the scout cannon.
Did you-?
Right, it's a one-use item, by the way.
Oh, damn.
I know that.
And it's useless.
Erm ackshually,
It's not a one use item.
It does not become use-
\less afterwards
>:(
Well, that sucks.
Hehehehahaha
"Never abandon a friend in need!"
What's this?
(scoffs) hehehehe
(slips)
Wurgh!
Bleh
oh that's alien cum right there
urghhh!
wurghhh!
Ahhhh!
Help!
I'm being stuck!
okay what happened
God damn it.
heheh
I've been poisoned.
get back in there
guys, let's stock up on food first
take a coconut half and
COOK IT
coconut???
cook??????
A Coc-
Hold on...
Coconut half.
kʊk (cook)
Huh??
Oh my god, it's gone...
you can cook it 'till it's Well Done
Oh!
What the?
Ooh, well done.
Oh, god damn it.
Did I used it already?
Ayyyyyyy.
Yup, you just throw the coconut at it
I threw Bing Bong-
I threw bing-bong right at the coconut
and it broke in half.
You know how when you're pinging at something,
it's supposed to ping where your cursor is at?
Mine doesn't.
Hehehahahahahah
Welp, something, something... skill issue I guess.
Well, you don't say.
Welp.
I need to figure out how to lock the mouse eventually.
*click*
(suspicious pushing)
*clack*
*click*
For very insi- what are you doing?
(conveniently placed jelly fish)
No, fuck off!
Nawthing~
Wow~
Ooh, first aid kit.
First aid kit.
And a rope.
I'll take that.
coconut?
Ooh, coconut.
coconut!
🎵Da coconut is a giant nut.🎵
🎵is a big big nut~🎵
editors note: this song hurts my brain
(bonk)
Ow...
Not me!
heheheh
I have two in my inventory right now and umm...
Wait. How do you-
quite-
chair gaming tips
only take
what's
useful btw
How do you keep it into number four?
Number four is if you have a backpack.
chair gaming tips
fourth slot
is for the
backpack
Oh~
Dash is our packed meal.
Yeah, you get one backpack
per objective milestone.
I realized what you said just now.
Here you go.
What? What did I say?
(leaving)
Rule 0
NEVER ABANDON A
FRIEND IN NEED!
-Scoutmaster Myres
Well, you can put it in my backpack.
I can't- it's pretty-
alright bye bye :D
Oh, right.
I can also open your backpack.
I told you he's our packed meal.
Oh, shut up. hehe
Heheheheh
All right, where we're heading?
Where's my girlfriend?
Hold on.
She's disappearing a lot.
la lalaa la lalaa
uhhh... is missing....
okay, (she)'s near- hehe
Stop speedrunning!
okay, over.
I've never seen such a slow speedrunner in my life.
(scoffs)
Oh my god, you're that far away.
My god.
It sounds like mosquito.
mosqui-
I'm gonna swat that bitch.
I'm very encumbered right now,
so my stamina ain't that high.
You are-
"Oh no, I'm over encumbered."
That's why I said to take only what's necessary.
You're overburdened.
You don't say.
-all of this stuff is necessary,
Hehehe
Including this random tampon
Hohoh-
HUH?
What?
shut it!
Heheha.
Shut it!
Hehehahahah
🎵Bear necessities~🎵
Oooh, rope cannon.
Cue clueless Mel...
Weeeee~
🎵I'll climb up all these something...🎵
Alright, guys, anyone, do you need any help the-
🎵I can get only bear necessities.🎵
close enough
I have-
Um, flares are useless.
* yea
* you can cook it in a camp-
fire to make it a good
food source tho
* you should try it :)
Oh...
Okay, in that case, let me just-
Ooooh, carrot-te.
(bonk)
Oh.
Actually... let's see...
Medicinal root.
You should have some-
We need everything.
Everything you see, just take it.
What the hell?
(the scientific method backfires)
Ay!
Do medicinal-
(Mocking Mel) "Lemme just walk into it~"
Actually, you know what?
I'm not gonna ask some questions.
(the scientific method pays off)
I dropped the trumpet
You guys can have it.
There we go.
That answers my questions.
Heheh
oh the balloon just fell down :(
So where are we supposed to go?
That way?
Ooh, scout cookies~.
up the mountain?
I mean, we're supposed to go up?
I mena, my mouth could be-
I mean, the name of the game is PEAK.
leaning towards that.
So I'm guessing we need to get to the peak.
(scoffs)
comedy
Something tells me we need to go up.
Oh god, dang it.
I guess you could say it's Only Up.
Oh~
No.
No, no, no.
That's copyright infringement.
(mini scoff)
Ow!
What the fuck!
Heeeeeeh hahahahah
Aeeueueuehhh~
I-I- (losing it)
You got poisoned?
I got a blowdart.
(honk mimimimimi~)
Are you alright down there?
No, fuck no.
(lmfao)
Would you like a medicinal carrot?
(grunt)
Fuck yeah, bitch.
wouldn't help
in this particular
situation :(
(only heals
poison)
(bo-womp)
Oh well, we didn't pick it up.
It's all the way back there.
Back w- (losing it)
Here?
Mwah!
She has Tourettes. And this is her tic.
hm
sho kyute :3
I have to press escape twice
just to reset my mouse position
Oh damn.
THE FOG RISES...
or else I'll actually click away and just fall off instead.
So that's how it works...
Oh.
foreshadow
/fɔːˈʃadəʊ,fəˈʃadəʊ/
verb
be a warning or indication of (a future event).
Oh, the zone is closing in.
That's actually what the right click is for...
The zone?!
Apex?
Yeah, that's a z-
No.
Sorry.
AHHHHH!
AHHHHHHHH!
oh-
she died?
aight i'm ditching her
No, I'm not dead.
I'm not dead yet.
Fuck-Fuck you guys.
you live, you learn
you live, you learn, you die
you live, you do not learn, you die
i live, i learn, i eat poison,
i die
and then i wonder why you didn't tell
me sooner,
and I curse you in the afterlife
he-heheheh
Bikini button.
(Bubble transition)
Ho ho, that was dangerous.
That-
Why'd you choose that?
I don't know,
Where?
I thought it was a short-.
where is bro at
Heheheheh
Bro said she knew a
spot 💀
I thought it was a shortcut.
I'm just following Dash.
wait where are you
what
oh yall are there
we're higher than you, speedrunner
we're higher than you, speedrunner (derogatory)
Hehahahahah
Uhhh, I like..
(Garry's Mod ragdoll noises)
Oh, hey, oh.
Oh, oh, okay.
(laughs)
Oh, um...
And bandages...
This is awkward.
(more foreshadowing)
I-I brought the-
I-I grabbed the chat.
Well, lead the way.
I wonder if my girlfriend's alive.
Let's climb-
I'll climb up to you eventually
Who knows.
Well, in that case...
Ehhh.....
Alright let's keep climbing.
(Thunder)
Rule 0
NEVER ABANDON A
FRIEND IN NEED!
-Scoutmaster Myres
Oh god!
Oh!
I was gonna give you a helping hand
but I right clicked and clicked into OBS.
Did you- dude?
yeah, you care more about OBS than your friends
No, the game, the mouse wasn't-
No! I highlighted the chat. No!
'Right...
No, I pressed the Windows key.
What?
(Jim Lahey falling down the stairs meme)
Just... get close to me, I cannot...
Ahh~
Phew, thanks.
Hey!
("Normal" Spongebob)
Hi, how are ya?
(Round Spongebob)
(scoff) Hehehehahah
(scoffs) Lol.
(I couldn't figure out what she said)
Oh hello.
Campfire!
🎵Sitting around the campfire,🎵
🎵and singing th' campfire song.🎵
(Steam achievement)
TROPICS
DAY TWO
🎵Spells (<-our) C-A-M-P-F-I-R-E-S-O-N-G song.🎵
Ooh, marshmallows.
Time to cook the marshmallow.
Alright, eat up.
AHH.
AAAAAAAAAA-
Oh, guys guys guys guys, guys
come here come here, come here.
Wait.
Coconut.
Guys the statue, the statue.
Let's touch the statue.
Omm..... (praying)
(statue crumbles)
Oh, what's this?
It's a faerie lantern.
faerie lantern.
I have no idea what it does frankly.
* this is actually a really
good healing item
* heals everything (inclu-
ding debuffs) over time
* worth carrying and can
save you in a pinch
(Ayo the Pizza here, spraining ankle meme)
Ow
You took fall damage.
Who took fall damage?
So not a gamer.
Such an idiot
I did.
Yea, you can trip and fall there.
You're not a gamer.
Oh my god guys
You are so not a gamer.
What a start.
what the f...-
I'm gonna drop this...
what IS this??
it looks like MY BALLS
HUH
Why don't we just go to the
center most one then?
Ow...
(More tripping)
I am not touching that.
Touching what?
You could try.
Oh god!
EUGH!
(FKNING GODZILLA)
(real, honest to god noises from KZF1)
Yo, who touched it?
Who touched it?
(Replay)
I don't know who did.
(It was KZF1)
Definitely not me.
Chicken?
Well I'm very poisoned so...
(soft sigh)
Thanks I guess.
no it's okay
it wears off eventually
your welcome :)
No I think...
thing that spreads poison
I think it accumulated from others.
Ow!
That's so weird.
Does anyone got medicines?
No no.
It wears off on it's own.
But slowly.
Which is a problem.
How long would that take?
Only usually is...
poison goes away
at the rate of
0.4 per second
Source:
PEAK wiki
OKAY WHO TOUCHED THE POISON CLOUD
AGAIN?
Uhh,
KZF1, you safe?
Ahhh~
OH GOD
Yeap
Yeap, I can't climb any higher than this.
Ooohhh, ohhh, ooohhh
I'll have to wait.
Oh shit.
Create a platform.
Ah.
Yea.
For you to climb-
Au!
Ough-!
Not again.
God damn it.
God damn it, KZF1.
No no, it was me, it was me.
I'm sorry. It was me.
"Sisyphus moment", real.
(laughs)
Umm,
it's possible to climb over here, guys.
guys? :(
Yes.
the grinch in the distance calling us
Heheheh
He's got-
uhh, I don't see anywhere to climb up here
That is true....
i think...
i think we need to go back.
thanks for the shortcut, Dash.
(giggles)
Oh, really now?
(smug laugh)
Sorry.
I'll wait...
Ah no thanks.
Is she alright though?
Wait where the hell is she?
Damn 😔
Wait where the hell is she??
WHERE DID MY BB
MY BB GOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
y'all okay???
Oh she's down there :D
Ugh, god dang it I-
Ugh
Did you step on the poison plant that
I pinged?
I think I did but-
I'm not sure
(if) the radius was big or my-
Am I just too thicc?
Hehahahah
i think you're just too thicc
Your thigh too thicc
Yeah, probably that.
(sigh)
the clap of my ass cheeks,
make the poisonous plant explode
did y'all go down the waterfall path?
are you- y-
(thump)
Ow!
If it were real life,
I would have a concussion.
AAAUUUUUUHH!
Where did my-
Where did she go?
who knows
I see a lot of v-
I'm below you, I'm below you
Below??
Tunnel???
What?
UWARgghhh
Okay...
I'm not in a-
What are you dow-
Oh you're DOWN there
okay
waithowdidyallgetup
Oh we were just up here
like literally the whole time.
Um...
We never-
oh, we just went up the
Naturally Formed Staircase™
over there
Oh you're using the vines.
(Smosh's Vines reference)
Vine~!
OOOH
WHAT ARE THOSE
SHROOMS
HELL YEAH
Hehehe
WE ABOUT TO
GET HIGH TONIGHT
I mean
(being forcefed)
the logical path would be going that way...
That face is-
NO
WHY
this place does look kinda SUS
(AMONGUS)
aaAAH
Do you want me to use this?
eugh-
h- UUUHGH
EUGHH
UUUGHHHH
Use this?
UGHHHH
Oh, careful of the balls,
th- (giggles)
wEEEEEEEE
the balls of death...
(doesn't grab the cliff)
eeUGH!
No, I clicked in the chat!
I fell to my death.
the foreshadowing finally
paid off
Hahahaha
Ah-
welp
Oh- Hello
tha- aHEM
I think I-
Well that's-
That's one-
That's one question answered.
eyyyyyyyy
Umm...
so...
how's it going
from the other side
sHUT UP
(giggle)
(aura farming)
help
HELP HELP HELP HELP
oh?
H
Oh my god.
Heheheh
Man this feels good to have an
actual good controller right now,
because the one- the old controller I had
was just...
YOU KNOW WHAT
You know what?
Dash, you've just convinced me-
-to just use a controller.
(not your computer)
(still not your computer)
With the mouse lock issue
constantly haunting me,
I'm just gonna use the controller instead.
OH-
WHY WOULD YOU-
woh
What?
WHY WOULD YOU THROW A BANANA PEEL
i didn't throw it, i dropped it
You sure about that?
YOU DROPPED IT DIRECTLY ON ME
I can see the evidence down there XD
YOU DROPPED IT DIRECTLY ON MY BODY
Ermm....
More like you...more like...
WHY WOULD YOU EVEN BRING A B-
WHY WOULD YOU EVEN KEEP A
BANANA PEEL WITH YOU
Heh hehehehe
i just ate a...
You touch that tralala....
Mmmm... my ding ding dong....
mMMmm you touch my tralala
No, what, what, hoeh?
hmmmm.....
Now, let me put this in the backpack.
Ooooooo
Oh, another chest!
Haunting in your dreams, moving in circles~
(laugh)
Oh my good
Oh my goodness
you're looking
you're looking really luggage-shaped
(scoff) HEHEHEH
Bruheheheheheh
HUH?
Looks like lunch on the other item next to you.
Ay, yo, food?
Yeah, food!
Ayo?
Yeah, there's food, there's food here.
Give me some food.
(GASM)
There's one more here.
There's one-
That barely filled anything!
(laughs)
What the heck?
Red clusterberry
oh-
The balloon popped
Aeh???
It's a...
How come did I get poisoned?
Ya touched something poisonous, genius.
Where?
(Giggles)
What's poisonous that touched me???
There's nothing poisonous near me!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Can you rope cannon to it
and then just nudge it or something?
Yea- I j-I just got poisoned again.
What did I get poisoned by?
(laugh) I just saw poisonous clouds.
wha-
What am I getting poisoned by again??
damn
depression, i suppose
(scoffs)
OH WAIT NO
I SEE IT NOW
there
there's a
(she meant leech)
lynch (leech)
on you
Oooooohhh
Someone get it off me!
Wait, stop moving!
Alright.
Well, the friendly ghost that haunts you has helped you once.
Yeah, make yourself useful.
You're a literal CCTV camera.
Shut up!
Bruh...
(giggles)
(giggle)
Bomb bomb bomb!
Just behind you.
Awh, yeah.
I almost moved BACK
whenyousaidtheresa(bomb)
Can you say "BOMB behind you" first
instead of saying "bomb bomb bomb" THEN
this crashout was a joke
if i see anyone being mean
i'm sending you straight
to guantanamo
Damn, it's such a disappointment that I lost my med kit.
Of all things that I lost.
Well, you still have your soul,
so that's a good start.
(laughs)
Treasure map.
Uhh...
Oh.
Alright, like the campfire boys.
Dear diary,
bad news!!!
The ship captain made an oopsy,
and
we've wound up crashed on this
mysterious island!
Alright, uhh now look...
Alright, what's this?
Dear diary, bad news!!!
The ship captain made an oopsie.
Oepsie woepsie o3o
de trein is stuk-
stukkie wukkie! owo
Oh wait, I'm already hungry. I see.
Lemme just...
Now, how are you poisoned?
(nom)
Ah-I don't know.
Is there another leech on you?
Ah!
There might be one.
There might be one on me.
drop the backpack
there wasn't
oh i haven't played this terrain yet
I have seen videos about this,
it's quite um...
a terrible place to play.
Let's just say.
It's fire.
Ahhhh!
There's a term: "getting sunburned"
if you know what I mean
Yup.
(laugh)
AHHHHH!
I'VE LOST
SO MUCH FROM THAT
Holy shit!
Does anyone have a med kit?
Are you sure we're not just allergic to vitamin D?
WAAA- TORNA-
Oh shit!
OH-
(hysterical laugh)
Get me out of here!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
Man, that scream was-
subscribe :)
back to the video
AAAAAAAAHHHHH
I'M HANGING ON FOR DEAR LIFE
I'll just drop down, why not
Anyone?
If you can hear me, just drop (down).
I'm alive!
I'm right here.
(laugh)
i got all the way down
good thing there was a
I'm down here as well.
WALL
right next to me
We're down here.
Oh my god.
I don't need an antidote.
Just a reminder....
to...
not touch the cactus.
it's gonna...
prick you, idk
Okay.
wow
how did you know that
Watch out for the tornadoes though while you're in the cactus... area
You don't say...
You don't want to be sent flying into a...
(laugh)
TORNADO
CACTI IN THE MESA
these are bad
for you!!!!!!!!
(applause)
We got sucked up by a tor-
Ah!
-nado.
We got sucked up by a tornado
Oh, you have to remove each one individually.
Yep.
Yeah, that's pretty funny, huh?
(laugh)
Any more (thorns)?
You don't say...
(slap and OUH!)
AHH!
Oh, this is pretty sketchy.
I need a med kit after this.
(I need a medic bag)
Oooo~
I'm gonna be red as fuck after this.
Oh, god dang it.
(Half life train noises)
I got prickled
AHHHHH
OHHHHH!
AAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHH
Oh, shit.
Thank-
Whoa, tornado's on the way.
I don't have one.
All right, let's get moving, let's get moving.
A Tornado Warning has been issued for the following areas:
🎵Hensonn - Sahara🎵
Umm...
I think it's coming toward us
The Mesa Biome
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run,
AAAAAAAAAAAAAA
run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
AHHHHH
AAHHHHHHHHHH!
Goodbye.
Sayounara, I'm on a cacti.
Alright, alright, help me help me,
I'm behind you, I'm behind you, I'm behind you
AAAAAHHHHHH
This was not the holiday trip I was expecting.
(laugh)
(giggle) You don't say...
Uh...
Are you alive?
I was so low on health already in the middle of the...
(Crash)
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
OH-
(RIP the gang)
(rustle)
no
(laughs)
All I heard from my girlfriend is a no and then
HA HAHAHAHAH
ATTEMPT
TWO
once more, with feeling
(It appears the containment system
has completely failed.)
heeeeyyyyyyyyy
we arrived at our new resort
(sigh)
Welcome to the Bahamas.
Welcome to Bangladesh.
Welcome to Baja blast.
What???
Then, let's go.
oh my god not the bugle again
Damn.
I'm gonna cook the three coconuts with me.
There we go.
Right, I got three whole coconuts with me.
All of them cooked.
Take this
No, I don't have space anymore.
I got three whole coconuts.
Did you hear me?
Here, have this.
whazzat
(bonk)
you missed, idiot
Coconut.
no she didn't
(buzz)
I did hit your face, dumbass.
yea she hit him
(ding dong! correct!)
you still missed, idiot
she still didn't miss
(buzz)
Obviously one can't climb with a coconut in the hand.
(sus)
What are you-
Oh?
Eeeh.
Grand Theft Auto.
Somebody made an oopsie.
Please.
Let me- lunge
O-Oh no.
Oh no.
Help, help, help help,
(gremlin noises)
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
What do I do? What do I do?
Are you okay, do you need food?
(giggles)
Okay
My health is...
I literally just dropped down to like...
50%.
Hello down there~
I have little to no health as well.
7 minutes into the run btw
yea, im on-
How low are you?
Uh...
About 25%.
You mean like your health?
Ehh.. no, like the red bar.
Overall bar.
The bar overall.
Yeah.
You have 25% left, okay.
(Mykoreandic reference)
Thank you.
I have no idea why but
but the hologram that comes out of the rope
looks like a flaccid-
family friendly
(this is from the birdbrain music video)
penis
(Teto AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA)
Oh wait behind you. Behind you.
Hmm?
Does that...
Does that way work tho?
I see leg.
I SEE LEG!
Like...
Oh wait. Oh that's your-.
Oh that's your ping.
(cough)
Sorry.
I thought it's someone's leg.
Okay.
(sigh)
Apparently I'm hallucinating.
Oh don't tell...
Don't tell me that only goes down and it doesn't go up.
hi how are ya
I can hear them-
(lol)
MARCO
(unintelligable)
What?
(giggle)
Marco!
They don't polo at us huh?
MORALE BOOST!!
Morale boost?
Did they-?
ehhhhhhh~
I'm trying to fi...
I'm trying to think of some-.
Why am I shivering?
Probably because of hunger.
it wasn't
(boo-womp)
-for me to climb up here-
Okay. I got more energy.
Ohhhh, nevermind. There are...
uhh...
erm...
I can see why because there are...
I think there are skeletons?
(Hells Kitchen Dramatic sound)
Spawning?
Oh?
Did-Did one of them die?
I just...
I just heard...
I just heard a ghost near us.
Right. Um...
With that said...
Oh wait... Do you still have the...
Hello!
Do you still have the rope spool?
I have
i havea to pee
(pufferfish eating carrot)
Oh!
Spool.
And then...
Is that enough?
That's more than enough.
But how can you...
oh-oh-oh
Woah-ohoh!
(full on panic)
Thanks for watching!
(Stream end bgm?)
I'M JUST KIDDING
DON'T LEAVE YET
(Pear teto)
How's KZF1 though?
we haven't seen him in a while
W-Where's my girlfriend?
(LIVE CHAIR REACTION)
I have no idea.
(bathroom)
are you alright down there
No we're not!
We've been Marco-ing for a while!
sounds like you're having
a wonderful time :)
What?
sounds like you're having
a wonderful time
(scoff) shut the fuc-
ah, he's sayin-
Hello there!
So how's things up there?
oh, you wanna know why i died?
Why?
you know that morale boost ya'll got?
Yeah?
yeah so
I summoned some unspeakable monster
that threw me off the entire thing
and killed me
The scoutmaster?
Name: The Scoutmaster
Sex: With me (-Editor)
Pronouns: was/were
Profile:
> I didn't add a
picture to avoid spoilers for the
NonPeakers
> You've probably
seen it's name
without realiziing though
> Did anyone hear
> that fucked up
> sound or was that just me
to give you all that morale boost
yeah
I thought it would at least help yall
but um
Nope, It did not
No, I-
It's not enough to be honest.
I think y'all should eat and then...
I think you should eat and then...
that should be enough to climb.
Look at my...
No, that's not enough.
Look at my damage and you tell me do I have enough?
Yeah, I made that with more damage than you.
I just ate everything I had.
I have to s-
Go- go down a bit.
Yeah, I have to smash that for a bit.
(smash)
OOOH
OH SHIT
Dash, need any nourishment?
GET ME OUTTA HERE
There's the fogs, will it kill us?
Fogs- fogs don't kill.
They just blur our vision.
We're not at the mes-
* fog does kill you
over time
* it afflicts 2.5 Cold
per 2.4 seconds
Oh no, it WILL kill you.
We're not at the Mesa, right?
Does it?
Oh, the fog WILL kill you.
Oh, it's like the...
It's like the...
It's like the zone, the lava.
Yup, yeaa... It's gonna kill us either way so..
Welp, sayounara!
(giggle)
Why not?
Welp, they're dying.
Might as well die of tragic death
Weeeeee!
So, how's things?
because you took-
because you two took so long
Rule 0
NEVER ABANDON A
FRIEND IN NEED!
- Scoutmaster Myres
a green man was chasing me
wanted to strangle me to death
We couldn't find anywhere the fuck to climb.
You-
Fuck you.
(to be) fair though, we are Truly Struggling™
down there with 60% health GONE
(laughs)
ah
I wonder how that happened
🎵Good Kid - Premier Inn🎵
Here we have-
We're witnessing a human chicken
????
in it's natural habitat.
Climbing up-
It looks so funny from this perspective.
heheheh
Climbing up-
Oh well.
-the Dreadful Mountain™, in search
for identity
No wait,
This-
This was-
This is un-
(un)fortunately not called Mount Celeste.
🎵Lena Raine - Resurrections🎵
🏳️‍⚧️Trans Pride!🏳️‍⚧️
And it's haunted-
and is still haunted by three Christmas spirits.
Well, at least I'm alive.
We're jolly-
The Past, The Present-
We're happy and jolly.
(laughs)
The past, the present, and the future.
Heheheheh
I may be surrounded by three annoying ghosts,
but at least I'm still alive.
Hey look, a medkit!
(laughs)
Oh hey!
Sharing is caring, am I right?
Communism!
I know, right?
Oh shit, I see it.
(laughs)
Alright, get going boy, get going.
I gotta book it.
(laughs)
He's very high right now.
Heheheh
The green man's not here.
The green man ain't here.
That's great.
So, statue?
Alright.
I activated it earlier.
Oh? What the?
It's already activated.
Oh well.
There we go I guess.
Welp, we're goin-
Why did you touch the statue before we all got up?
Ah shit...
Well, one and all then.
Ope, uh...
Good luck camp finding.
Go, Brian, go.
Welcome to my Let's Play.
(laugh)
It's just me.
Top of the morning to ya laddies.
Nobody else.
the chicken special
🎵Resident Evil Director's Cut Dualshock OST - Mansion Basement🎵
Oh yeah, by the time this one is over
there's gonna be a new map.
Oh yeah, yeah.
There was a countdown for that on the main menu.
wow
Yeap
great
a new map
just wonderful
poison
Oh god.
Oh my go-
Oh my god.
Poisonous flora everywhere.
There's one here.
There's one there.
Kon-Fauna (Ceres Fauna reference)
man, this is heavy
You don't say.
The weight of our sins AND your backpack
man, now I know what it feels like
to be a Dasher
(laugh)
You don't say
Should I take the anus
or should I take the staircase?
Man, I need to catch a break or something.
At least you're playing a game, man.
(laugh)
(giggle)
yea...
At least you're playing the content
that we're missing out.
(giggle)
(laugh)
Wa-hey.
He's our content.
niceeeeeeee
Yay.
Ugh.
Oh, hey.
What's up, guys?
Hello.
EVERYONE CAN PLAY
THE GAME NOW
(ding)
EVERYONE CAN PLAY
THE GAME NOW
(ding)
EVERYONE CAN PLAY
THE GAME NOW
(ding)
EVERYONE CAN PLAY
THE GAME NOW
(ding)
EVERYONE CAN PLAY
THE GAME NOW
(ding)
EVERYONE CAN PLAY
THE GAME NOW
(ding)
EVERYONE CAN PLAY
THE GAME NOW
(ding)
Now with meat shields
Haven't seen you in such a long time.
Even now we are hungry
Right, let's light the campfire.
Energy drink
Morale boost
Oh yeah.
Alright.
Unfortunately, I have to eat the marshmallow immediately.
If not, I'd be too hungry.
There we go.
Owie.
That berry really does something, huh?
Yikes.
Umm...
I hear a tornado.
Oh, I can see it.
Oh, it's coming our way.
I see it now.
It's coming our way.
Hug the wall.
Oh boy.
Woah.
Here it comes!
Grab the wall.
Oh, it's coming towards us again.
Go go go go go go
Actualy, where's-
Run, run, run, run, run.
where's-
Just keep running.
Where's th-
Where's your girlfriend?
I don't know.
She probably went ahead or something.
She ditched us.
(omg bruh, aw hell naw)
Rule 0
NEVER ABANDON A
FRIEND IN NEED!
-Scoutmaster Myres
How did she?
I don't think she...
Oh, nevermind.
She actually ditched us.
(what the fuck man)
(giggle)
Rule 0
NEVER ABANDON A
FRIEND IN NEED!
-Scoutmaster Myres
There she is-
Ow, help.
It's a miracle for what you're getting.
Guys, help.
How the hell did you jump over there?
Lunge.
Lunge over.
Oh
Lunge sideways.
(pushes)
(falling)
Excuse me.
Oh god!
Sorry.
You don't say...
I'm gonna go there.
Just to reach for that.
How the hell do you even go down there?
Okay.
Oh-hohohoh
Pure guts, I tell you.
Ho!
Pure guts.
Oh-hohohohohoh
Okay.
You got some BALLS on you.
i don't know how he died
Now the tides have turned.
We three are the ones alive.
Hehehehehehe
Yep, I've carried enough in the second match.
Hahahaha
Heh, you SURE have the guts to tell us.
(giggle)
(laugh)
Of course I do.
What do you think about that?
Ehh, up to you.
Do you literally just chuck that at a wall?
Yes, it's a...
Oh-wow.
It works like magic.
It's a natural enlarging fungus.
If you can, stick it (piton).
Okay, sticking.
Stick the hook.
Eh!
There we go.
Nice.
Now drop-p down.
If you can.
Wait, hold on to the hook before you climb-
Oh~!
Careful, careful, careful.
I'm dying.
You're off your goddamn mind.
Wooooo
Okay- Oh my god!
Who grabbed my hand? That was such a lifesaver.
I've lost NONE of the health.
I grabbed-
Oooooh, what's that?
Is that dynamite?
Or is that another chest?
I feel that's a cursed chest.
I feel like that's a cursed chest.
Is it?
A cursed chest?
It looks ominous, don't you think?
Why do I think they color (them) with that?
Let's have a look. Let's have a look.
I don't know
Ancient luggage.
we don't have any-
Oh god, that might be cursed.
Just open it.
See what it does.
AH-
i couldn't think of a joke
What's in it?
I'll take it.
Anti rope spool.
I'll pick this up.
What?
Ooooh, wait that was.
Anti...
That's the-
That's what'll get us up from...
Oh, it's an upside down thingy.
Is it... but...
Oh, that's awesome.
It's the upside down spool.
(laugh)
That's funny.
Hold on, let me just see how it looks like
when I spool it.
It's not that tall, I think.
But yeah, it brings you up.
LUNGE
JUST A LITTLE CENTIMETRE
okay
Nevermind.
"Remedy Fungus"?
What the hell is this?
Oh.
What the hell?
It only throws.
Oh, that's poisonous.
* it's not poisonous
* heals injuries immediately
and overtime
* removes poison
overtime
* removes spores
Oh, okay. Hold on.
it's ok though! as long as
they don't throw it away
Let me just... step out (of the way).
No. No wait, is it?
wait what is she doing
Step away.
oh
I don't think that...
oh well
Oh.
Oh, it makes a cloud.
Yup.
Just as I thought.
Oh, is it-
Aw, not the sun...
Oh, god.
Okay, it IS fine.
Nevermind.
Caution, it is steering (towards) here.
Oh, god.
Oh, oh, god.
Then, what-
What do we do?
Get down, get in, right now.
it's every shut-in's nightmare
🎵Carmen Twillie & Lebo M - Circle of Life🎵
(Mel's buthering) Ahhhh, Zerveniaaaaa.
*Actual in Zulu & Swazi: Nants'ngwenyaaaa-)
Wait, so what are you doing now?
Do you just wait for night?
Yeah, you're gamers.
Yes~
What do you expect?
Well, that's fine then.
Oh, my god! The tornado.
If it comes to here, I'll be very...
I'll laugh my ass off.
I'm laughing my ass off.
If this comes-
I'm sure it'll be fine
subtle foreshadowing
Oh, no.
Your gamer skin can't handle it.
Here, here, here.
Okay.
Where?
Oh, the sun is rising more and more.
Oh, down here.
Okay.
Oh, I- I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
T- In a hole down here.
Oh, my god. We're so sunburned right now.
Ohh~
We're so sunburned.
Woah, you guys pushed me out!
it feels like i'm looking at a
bunch of mudcrabs
hiding from the sun
I-I-I-
I revived and you IDIOTS immediately
pushed me out.
Are you serious?
(Minecraft cave sound)
Okay, this pathway is still doable.
(dnuod evac tfarceniM)
Oh, bruh.
I have enough-
I have enough extra stamina to do this.
OH NO
You have an energy drink.
Oh, yeah.
So, if I just use...
Oh wait, yeah, I can-wait, I got it, I got it.
I'll use the energy drink.
Only one person can use it though.
Yeah, I-I'll use it and then I have a rope spool
and then I'll use...
Yeah, spool down.
Do we spool up?
I literally have no.
I guess...
Just do it.
No choice with spool up.
Okay.
Spool~
Oh my god.
Okay, we need a better spot to spool from.
Like this.
Probably- eugh -ugh -ugh -eugh
Oh?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh?
So do-so-so-so do we tie (a) knot?
How do we tie it?
Tie it up here then.
RT (Tie knot).
Oh, it has to tie-
it has to be tied from like a foothold.
Okay, I get it now.
(plop)
There we go.
How does this work scientifically?
Oh no!
it doesn't
Wait, there's a crate behind you.
There's a chest behind you.
Go get that.
Wait, getting my girlfriend first. Okay.
Okay, okay.
Get the chest first.
It might have food or energy.
(gremlin noise)
Ugh, just a little bit.
Oh, you did the iconic move.
Flop like a fish.
Oh no, I'm burned.
SpongeBob SquarePants!
Oooooh~
Lollipop and a spool!
The sun is currently up, so...
Hmm.
Welp, GG.
Okay, GG.
Yeah, I think we're cooked here.
GG.
This is a GG.
Oh, hi.
Green Man (Dasher)
(mimicking Mumei) Oh, hi.
Eurh, my god.
Th-, there's a hole there.
I- I literally can't go there.
Wouldn't it be fun- wouldn't it be funny if I just launched you over.
Oh, the cannon. That could work
Yeah, I have a cannon.
I have a sliver of stamina,
if I touch sun
I will DIE
Okay.
(lol)
(laugh)
That sounds so wrong...
that's the most gamer sentence
i've ever heard
(laugh)
i think it's about time
to just go
kill yourself
(Thunder)
Wait, but...
Just put- No, no, no, no, no.
If you wanna die, die, die majestically.
(place)
Heheheh
Ready?
You light it up and you jump in.
L-
LIT!
Be the bird you are meant to be!
(laugh)
Wait, it still works.
You went-
(boom)
I'm stuck.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm stuck in here.
Oh, oh-
Ahhhhhh!
Nope, I'm- I'm- I'm dead.
I am actually dead inside the cannon.
Hmm, did they die in a-
Ey, yo?
hold e
Have done.
hold e to win
hold e
Heheheheh
Ahhhh
my god.
have we improved
from last time?
I can't tell.
it's roughly the same
A+ for effort!
Maybe?
hElLo
Nice to meet you :)
Hey, I got a clutch-
I got a new badge.
It's the clutch badge.
Hey, I finally got one that-
That's-
That's actually so me right now.
(applause)
Tech Wizardess
Wow, a hat?
No way.
You did it!
Yay!
We got further than we ever did before.
Let's go!
Another round?
The sun-
The sun is killing me.
I think I'm fine with another round.
(mini scoff)
ATTEMPT THREE
(plane crash)
Wow...
New map?
Nothing beats a Jet2 Holiday
(laugh)
Oh wait, the map hasn't reset yet.
What?
Oh, probably we have to leave first-
we reopen the lobby and probably the map has reset.
Damn, so you all wanna try a new map for the
day
'Right, let's-
do you just wanna commit to this?
No need
ouch
What the?
Right, let's re-
I'm fine with either.
Let's reset.
Alright.
a
Oh?
I clicked way too quickly.
Oh, new island in 27 minutes.
Now's not the time yet.
Oh, it's not yet.
Well, that sucks.
I walk a lonely road~
(Reference: Green Day - Boulevard of Broken Dreams
(vocalizing)
Hehe. Sorry.
And there you have it, folks.
(singing)
🎵Thomas The Tank Engine Theme ending🎵
the end
(for real this time)
editors note:
she kinda ate that
on beat and everything
(after a brief message)
What a timing.
PEAK timing
um
Unfortunately, the Steam servers have all
died
and unfortunately, none of us can get
connected
So!
Oh I can connect, actually
????
Ergh?
there was a longer message
about the hiatus in november
but i took too long to edit
this so
oops
With that said,
Thank you so much for watching!
🎵Outro: Syarou - Shuwa shuwa Honey Lemon 350ml🎵
Otsu Melo deshita (It's been ya girl Mel)
おつメロでした
See you guys!
Have a good day, night, whatever.
Bye byeee
have a PEAK day
Yeet!
Remember to stay hydrated
we'll never know what he said
Thanks for watching!
Edited by: @wasvreta on YT
QC-ed by: me! (Mel!)
[Ko-fi Nov 2025]
StickTV
Xandra~
Robi
Natalie
Thank you so much
for watching!
Thanks for
supporting me financially!
MeloriTensei
転性メロリ
Wanna translate for Mel?
Check the link in the desc for GitHub repo!
[Ko-fi Dec 2025]
StickTV
Xandra~
Natalie
Tove
[Ko-fi Jan 2026]
Xandra~
Natalie
StickTV
[Ko-fi Feb 2026]
Tove
Xandra~
Natalie
[Ko-fi Mar 2026]
Tove
StickTV
Xandra~
Natalie
Tove
[Ko-fi Apr 2026]
StickTV
Xandra~
Natalie
(singing)
🎵Thomas The Tank Engine Theme ending🎵
fin
(for real)
Sorry.