Hey, it's been a while.
By the way, thank you new and returning viewers
for checking out my previous CachyOS video
and having a talk with me.
It was pretty relaxing.
So let's get to the topic.
Where was I in the past few months?
You see, to new viewers, you might not know much.
So I'm gonna get you up to speed.
I called a hiatus for my regular game streams
to restructure my stream content.
With personal expectations that
I'll still regularly release videos,
but the videos have not been out.
What happened during it?
In the first month of a hiatus, which was December of 2025,
I began working on sorting out my messy setup
in my Unraid NAS server,
which is a mess.
If you are not one to regularly keep things tidy,
have a look at your desktop and you tell me what you see.
Yeah...
That's what I meant.
But at a larger scale that came biting back at me
at my workflow efficiency.
Towards the end of December,
I realized I needed far more time than usual.
So I began laying out things that I needed to work on.
Which is a few sets of parts that you saw in the Trello post
that I recently put up in YouTube community post.
I had seen the sheer horrors
of the things I had to work on.
I gotta lock the heck in.
Fast forward.
New Years happened.
Fireworks popping everywhere.
I took a breather and prayed,
Everything's gotta go smoothly to plan.
Until it didn't.
My relative got hit by a vehicle and was admitted to hospital.
They lived alone, so after they discharged,
they had to stay over at my place
because my family was the only reachable and closest relative.
But this is Asia.
We don't have an abundance of rooms.
So in times of emergency, we let them live in my studio room
I've recorded and worked in all these times.
Thinking it's going to be a few weeks thing,
I just moved a small amount of my stuff.
Namely my mic, my mouse, my Steam Deck
over so I can continue working on server stuff.
Only to learn that we're living in the AI bubble.
The laptop I used to work on stuff,
remember that CachyOS laptop?
began terminating my active programs and I realized one thing.
I'm out of RAM for the work that I was doing.
In a miniature panic, I quickly get RustDesk functional and working,
which thankfully, did.
Crisis averted.
I can work on lighter stuff that needs more browser tabs.
As time passes and a couple of revisits into my studio room
to check on stuff, I sense a suspicious smell.
In secret, I had a chat with my mom on what's going on,
and my mom seems to agree with me.
There's a hint of tobacco
in the smell of my entire studio room.
So for a few days, we've monitored the situation
and been secretly observing what my relative's
been doing behind our backs.
With clear and concrete evidence,
we've came to the conclusion that
they smoke in my studio room
with no airflow.
I remember vividly that my mom had made clear to them
that we had a no smoking policy in this entire house,
but they've broken that one rule.
My respect for this said relative
is shattering right before my eyes.
(Sigh)
During my personal research, I found that third-hand smoking
can cause problems to anyone who comes into contact
with objects that nicotine touches,
which stays for an extremely long time.
Now if you know any content creator, or heck,
even just an average gamer,
you know how difficult it is
to take down an entire setup to clean every surface
that the nicotine touched,
let alone getting baking soda, vinegar,
or worse, trisodium phosphate, and clean every surface.
Knowing that they had smoke in my studio room
and in the bathroom attached to it,
the idea of needing to clean any speck of nicotine
off of every visible surface
is going to set me back a month or two,
heck, even three more months.
And that's on top of what few months I projected needing
for my background restructuring I was initially working on.
After a few hours, I calmed down,
figured I might have overreacted,
but things gone way worse days after.
In the midst of my occasional internal rage against them,
backup came.
A distant relative family came over to visit him,
and my mom had a plan to quietly confiscate their cigarettes
and hand it off to the relative for removal.
And hand it off to the relative for removal.
At the end of the reunion,
they planned to confront them directly.
During the confrontation, they flat out denied
that they have smoked,
and was perplexed that we knew there was one cig missing
from the first time we checked.
To some of y'all who think it's an invasion of privacy,
screw y'all!
I own this damn house
and I made the smoking policy pretty dang clear.
Well, technically my mom.
And I'm acting within my right to know
if they've smoked in my premise.
With those specific reactions,
all trust I had on them had been lost.
I thought of giving them a little chance
considering there should be no cigs anymore.
Right?
Until days later.
I spotted something sitting on the pile of
personal valuable belongings of theirs.
An e-cigarette.
Knowing I'm gonna have a fit and that'll be bad,
I quickly relayed it to my mom,
and closed myself in the bedroom that I've been working on
and just focused on working on the NAS.
Within a day, I learned from her that
she has confiscated the e-cig quietly too.
Pair that with their surprised reaction to the fact that it's missing.
Of course they have no guts to ask us about it,
because that'll mean they'll admit that the cig was theirs.
It's been a month since the incident,
and things seem to have stabilized.
Another thing that has been eating me silently.
Burnouts.
You see, when I was moving into this new place,
I got myself two rooms out of the few
in the apartment that we bought.
Just so I could solve this long-standing psychological issue
of having the work and play in one single room at my old place.
By separating work and non-work,
I felt a nice release from what feels like eternal work.
If I see my work table right when I wake up...
Ugh, that ain't a good feeling.
But with my laptop sitting just across my bedroom,
it's starting to feel a lot like my old place again.
Pair that to the fact that I've gotten used to a three-monitor setup,
I had at maximum: two,
or at minimum: one.
Instead, these early few weeks had been my most
unproductive weeks in my lifetime,
with barely any motivation working at all.
I was also at my all-time low.
Fast forward to a few weeks after that,
my relative offered to take them in
for periods where the recheckup date gap
spans further than a few days.
So we took up on that offer.
After a few weeks, they were cleared to work
and discharged, and is back to their own place.
Thankfully.
Now, with you being able to watch this video in itself is a blessing,
because as of the time I published this video,
my entire setup had been torn down thoroughly, cleaned thoroughly,
and the NAS is somewhat sorted, but is still a mess.
I might have to redo that, if it's necessary.
Now, I hope to get back to the groove of content creation,
but we'll see what happens first.
Now, with that long story out of the way,
I'd like to cap it off with:
I greatly appreciate y'all sticking around with me.
Despite my silence at times,
and constantly looking forward to my content regardless,
it's been a crazy rough start of 2026 for me.
But I hope it gets better from here.
While I can't promise a date of return, from what I'm seeing,
I predict I might return probably around May or so.
It's just speculation, but there will be a new video
when I can confirm that I can continue working comfortably.
There might be a stream around then.
With that said, thank you so much for your patience.
And once again,
OtsuMelo deshita (It's been ya girl Mel).
Peace.